Bhauji how are you living with your old husband you are
so young you are so lost you don't
reach there what do you do with it I am just a
joke government job I am a husband earning 45000 rupees a
month amazing 45000 rupees a month I
wear it in my ears Bhaiya then I get tea in the train then I
spend a song every month
listen sir brother I am not wearing it sir a thief
steals it from the train and wears it as dowry I don't
know another thief Bhauji you should not be upset at all then
give the dowry of the one with a government job you are full of gold and silver from top to bottom our
man is me listen to me one thing you
[ __ ]
brother you are
fighting with me
[laughter] you
saw it was not right or
wrong tell me tell me
then sister fights more
sister fights in the house
you are watching should you go and take food or else beat
me or beat me I have not taken food [laughter]
how should I eat [music]
today I will see how I can eat if not you sit down
[laughter] I have put the servant
on the trap and take the food  B.
Go and do your duty
[Music]
You sit,
why am I sitting quietly,
hey, if you sit in front of a man after eating,
love increases, a man eats more of his sorrow, the
people of the village keep themselves away and laugh and whisper
in the dealer's ears, I bought so much gold, hey, I
bought it after a fight, sit down,
I want it today, right now, I'm going to the market,
leaving my gold purchase,
yes, leaving it, are you
mad, yes, I'm going to go, right now, I'm going,
okay
[Music]
one, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14,
[Laughter] then come and take something, it's
2000 less [Laughter]
Babu, cutting the wheat,
cutting the wheat [
Laughter] if the
wheat is not cut, then two men will go, sit and
[ __ ] me [
Laughter] if you don't agree, then take the goods and give the money,
okay, if you don't give ₹000, then give me one from the place, okay,
give me the place, Didi, Babu, from a thief Chuhar, I'll take
only the goods, give me the money, maintain a relationship, the
rest you take, Baba, do
n't you  [Music]
[Music]
Okay guys, tell me one thing,
how many times have you actually fished? If we
say that my friends and I go fishing every day
and don't do that fishing, then what do you think?
Maybe you've heard about that fishing game that's
so viral in India right now. And
believe me, there's a solid
reason for it to go viral. You can catch such a big fish that the
bigger the catch, the bigger the crazy
reward. And trust me, I can
catch such a big fish that I'll take out a
helicopter, a joint ice machine, and
even send a massive robot out of the game. But to be honest, it's
not that hard.
This game is going super viral right now and every day
more than a million people play it on India's most
trusted and popular gaming platform.
And to be honest, I
personally trust this platform.
And yes, guys, I have a
little secret, like you can
catch the biggest fish and
get a chance to unlock mega rewards. And
guys, just pin the link in the comments.  If it is
available then hurry up brothers,
open the file, register and
claim the mega reward, otherwise everyone else will also
try to get hold of their previous joint fee, so go quickly brothers, what should I get, I will
ask someone [laughs] what should I
show in Sona's ear,
a little lightly
[laughs] so the one I
liked, I
showed in the ear, the jhumka Madrasi top
earring,
now show me the new design that has come, oh oh do
n't touch it, why did you touch it, I do
n't mean a thief [laughs] I will get the stuff
later, I will see
[sangeet] I will see
or I will see, it is
very good, so
we all took it by paying money, I took it,
but take the upper one in the ear and take the lower one,
yes take two, brother, weigh both one and one
[music]
[music] it is worth Rs.
73000,
together, that is 1 lakh and I will not take 10% banking
charge, that is
1 lakh, oh brother, what should I do with the same roll
[laughs]
and something else
Bhabhi ji said one thing, looking at my face,
I have a necklace of the same color as my face,
look at the
neighbors and seeing everyone else, oh my
god, it's so beautiful, now I will take the necklace, I will take it, if you hadn't brought
anything, then sister would have felt like going and bringing the stuff, Dada, I will take the
stuff,
I will take the
stuff, oh my
god, how could you have
closed the shop, Maharaj, today I am a
shopkeeper in the village, [laughter]
[music]
where would you go, where would you go,
first give me the money, money, oh my god,
how much money, before going to sleep at night, whisper
in Sona's ear,
go and take it from me, I will take it
from the old lady, you will work, daughter, I am
young, I will become an old lady, don't fight with me,
father, don't understand, when you hear the
chatter in front, then I said, buy it from the
goldsmith, whisper in my ear,
go and buy it from the goldsmith, it's just a matter of work, call me, buy it from the goldsmith,
father earns gold and silver every month at home, father, I am the
husband, I earn and keep it
[music]
not a goldsmith
[music] I am waiting for you since
long brother  You [ __ ], I don't
need it,
I will bury the money in my house and give it to you every month. The
old lady sits there blabbering like this all day long. I keep blabbering and making you sit.
[Music] You
showed me the
earrings, showed me the
earrings, I took
out one design after another, one design after another, I liked it, did you not?
[Music] I saw it, look
how beautiful it is [Music] If you leave it,
I saw it, look how much it has become,
see which one did you take, I asked you, take
both of them, how much is it [laughs]
Now tell me, how much is it, I would have taken both of them,
once it slips out of your hands, you wo
n't get it back.
[Music]
I saw it was worth ₹59300, ₹44000,
₹9000,
so I bought it for ₹70 from the
gold fair, in just six days, I wore it, I
wore it for life, it left a stain on my body, but I did not
give any stain, I don't speak as much as I was intelligent
[Music]
After 60's 400  If you don't give it for 10,000
, I will give it to you Maharaj, if I say 20,000, then you will get
200 rupees gold. Shut up a
lot and say, take it, Maiji, go, Maiji,
where will you run? I saw this very spot, Maiji, Maiji,
Maiji, the
old lady in law, I will give it to you, be afraid of me, as if the
price is less, get up and run away,
listen, and the next day tell the old lady, where will you run, it's not
right, early in the morning,
oh sister, the village's Burwahar [music], if
I put gold in the ear in the bank today, the banker says the gold is
good, the banker says, who sells the gold in the village, if you give me at what
rate, it will be a little less, the
banker says, I will take it, get it washed,
I don't want anything, go and talk to the biker, I will give you
stuff to wear in the ear,
what is the need to load it in the bike, you are a man,
we know our women's songs and
drink alcohol, oh my god, oh my god, oh
brother,
move away, I fight, don't fight, it's
bad  I am staying on the
cot
[laughs] Now I don't face beating early in the morning
My day passes by,
one jora, two jora, three jora
This is what happens, you
disappear from me Give me a big way I accuse you of theft,
keep my stuff,
oh brother,
beat me up
[music]
Even if you could have opened a shop selling potatoes and Kachri, you could have
beaten the gold in the shop
[laughs]
[music]
Where have you taken it till now, oh I am here, I
heard,
see, both of us are very
happy today, what is the matter, what is the matter, wait, I sat and
saw, did I
fall, didi, oh my god, yes,
I am so satisfied, do
n't change the house yet
Sonia, when I got free from the gold and silver fort, I
built the house, then called the goldsmith, there is
no arrangement for it, cot [laughs]
Totally sitting on the cot,
go and take the cot
[music] On the
cot, I did one thing, spread the Tripali,
Maharaj, I
told Tripa, what kind of gold is needed in the house, I should
wear it regularly in the house, I should
not wear it always in the house, I did
not hear, if you give me gold, then sell it to Ramesh, goldsmith, after
coating it with gold,
see, the goldsmith will sell it  And sell the iron,
blacksmith, I am a goldsmith, I sell gold, blacksmith, I
sell iron, I take care of it with closed eyes,
if there is even 1% problem, I will take it and
throw it in your face, I will just show you,
yes, tell me, show me the anklets, I have
anklets in one of the best designs, I have
seen them in one of the best designs, I will just show you, see
how beautiful the design is,
look here brother, you show me, you show me, show me, what a
beautiful design,
Tika, oh my god, Tika [laughs], Nathiya, I have a
Nathiya, look, it's so beautiful,
sit and look at your father's ass, look
brother, oh brother, brother, I am
entangled in a loincloth all day,
who earns, so I keep wearing gold from top to bottom, if
I ask, then it's my goodness
[laughs]
brother, I
got the
video, brothers, please like it,
subscribe to the channel and comment, you will get a
gift, the winner of the first video is
Ravi Ranjan Kumar from Lakhra, East Champaran,
Motihari, got a gift, the second one is
from Phulwaria, Chhapra, District Chhapra  Their names are
Nazia Khan, thirdly Dheeraj Kumar who is from
Saran district, Sen Sara district, Parsa,
fourthly
Rouniak Alam who is from Uch village, Gopalganj,
and fifthly
Imtiaz Premi from Paharganj, New Delhi, so I got a gift, tell me
brothers, where did the gift reach Delhi,
so comment how did you like the video,
comment if you liked it, say I liked it, if you liked it, then I liked it,